I went down
مضيت إلى
to St. James Infirmary
إلى دار سان جيمس للعجزة
To see my baby there
لأرى طفلتي هناك
She was lying on a long wooden table
كانت تستلقي على طاولة خشبية طويلة
So cold, so still, so fair
باردة جدا وهادئة جدا وخائفة
I went up to see the doctor
وتقدمت لأرى الطبيب
"She's very low," he said
قال:" إنها ضعيفة جدا"
I went back to see my baby
وعدت لؤية طفلتي
Good God
ي إلهي
she's lying there dead
إنها تستلقي ميتة
I went down to old Joe's bar room
ونزلت إلى بار جو القديم
On the corner of the square
في زاوية الساحة
They were serving drinks as per usual
كانوا يقدمون الشراب كالعادة
And the usual crowd was there
والجمع المعتاد كان هناك
To my left stood Old Joe McKennedy
وإلى يساري وقف العجوز جو ميكيندي
His eyes were bloodshot red
كانت عيناه مضرجة بالدماء
He turned to the crowd around him
والتفت إلى الجمع حوله
And these are the words he said
وكانت تلك الكلمات التي قالها
"Let her go, let her go, God bless her
دعيها تمضي، دعيها تمضي وليباركها الرب
Wherever she may be
أينما كانت
She can search this whole wide world all over
فبإمكانها أن تبحث في هذا العالم بأكمله
But she'll never find another man like me
ولكنها لن تجد رجلا آخر مثلي
She can search this whole wide world all over
بإمكانها البحث في كل أنحاء العالم
And she'll never find
ولن تجد أبدا
another man
رجلا آخر
like me
مثلي
When I die, please God, bury me
حين موتي، أرجوك ياربي، ادفني
In my ten-dollar Stetson hat
في قبعتي ذات العشرة دولارات
Put a twenty-dollar gold piece on my watch chain
ولكن قطعة ذهبية بعشرين دولار في سلسلة ساعتي
So my friends know I died standing pat
حينها سيعلم أصدقائي أنني مت واقفا بشكل مناسب
Get six gamblers to carry my coffin
وسيحمل ستة مقامرين كفني
And six choir girls to sing me a song
وستغني لي جوقة من ستة فتيات أغنية
Stick a jazz band on my hearse wagon
وستضرب عصا فرقة الجاز على عربة كفني
To raise hell as I go along
لتوقظ الجحيم الذي أن أتجه اليه
Now that's the end of my story
الآن هذه هي نهاية قصتي
Let's have another round of booze
لنشرب الخمر ثانية
And if anyone should ask you
وإذا سألك أي كان
Just tell them I got
أخبريهم فقط بأنني حصلت على
the St. James Infirmary
أغاني دار سانت جمس
blues
الكئيبة